Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Reagan Books, 1968-1988 (Box 1-133)
  - 641-011-001. RNC: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Pref. in South Carolina 5th Congressional District, September 16, 1982 - September 18, 1982 (Box 28)
  - 641-011-002. RNC: Television Spot Study "Differences,", September 1, 1982 - September 1, 1982 (Box 28)
  - 641-011-003. RNC: Merge, December 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 28)
  - 641-011-004. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Carolina, July 15, 1986 - July 17, 1986 (Box 28)
  - 641-011-004. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Carolina, July 15, 1986 - July 17, 1986 (Box 28)
  - 642-008-001. RNC: A Survey of South Dakota Voter Attitudes, August 27, 1980 - November 2, 1980 (Box 28)
  - 642-008-001. RNC: A Survey of South Dakota Voter Attitudes, August 27, 1980 - November 2, 1980 (Box 28)
  - 642-008-002. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in South Dakota 1st Congressional District, April 6, 1980 - September 6, 1980 (Box 28)
  - 643-008-001. RNC: Tennessee 5th, September 1, 1980 - September 1, 1980 (Box 28)
  - 643-008-001. RNC: Tennessee 5th, September 1, 1980 - September 1, 1980 (Box 28)
  - 643-008-002. RNC: Tennessee Statewide Report from Eagles, January 1, 1981 - December 1, 1981 (Box 28)
  - 643-008-003. RNC: Voter Attitudes in Tennessee Extracted from 20 National Surveys, January 1, 1983 - May 1, 1984 (Box 29)
  - 643-008-004. RNC: A Banner Report Based On Merged 1984 Data for Tennessee, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 29)
  - 643-008-005. RNC: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Tennessee, October 6, 1986 - October 7, 1986 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-001. RNC: Tennessee Wave 2, September 10, 1980 - September 1, 1980 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-001. RNC: Tennessee Wave 2, September 10, 1980 - September 1, 1980 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-001. Reagan/Bush: Tennessee Wave 2, September 10, 1980 - October 1, 1980 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-002. RNC: Tennessee Tracking, October 1, 1980 - October 1, 1980 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-002. Reagan/Bush: Tennessee Tracking, October 1, 1980 - October 1, 1980 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-003. Reagan/Bush: Cross-Sectional Study: Tennessee, August 1, 1984 - October 16, 1984 (Box 29)
  - 643-009-003. RNC: Tennessee, September 1, 1984 - October 1, 1984 (Box 29)
  - 644-011-003. RNC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas 4th Congressional District, September 18, 1980 - September 19, 1980 (Box 29)
  - 644-011-004. RNC: 1st Texas Statewide Report From "Eagle" Surveys I through X, January 10, 1981 - August 14, 1981 (Box 29)
  - 644-011-005. RNC: 2nd Texas Statewide Report From 6 "Eagle"Surveys, September 1, 1981 - December 1, 1981 (Box 29)
  - 644-011-006. RNC: Voter Attitudes in Texas from 20 National Surveys, January 1, 1983 - May 1, 1984 (Box 29)
  - 644-011-008. RNC: A Banner Report Based On Merged 1984 Data for Texas, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 30)
  - 644-011-009. RNC: A Banner Based on Merged 1984-1985 Data, November 1, 1984 - November 1, 1985 (Box 30)
  - 644-011-010. RNC: A Study of Voter Attitudes in Texas + Special Clements Run, December 15, 1985 - December 17, 1985 (Box 30)
  - 644-011-010. RNC: A Study of Voter Attitudes in Texas + Special Clements Run, December 15, 1985 - December 17, 1985 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-001. Reagan for President: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Republican Voters in Texas, April 24, 1980 - May 2, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-002. Reagan for President Committee: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voters in Texas, June 24, 1980 - June 25, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-002. Reagan for President Committee: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voters in Texas, June 24, 1980 - June 25, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-003. Reagan/Bush: Texas Statewide Telephone Survey - Wave I, August 23, 1980 - August 24, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-003. Reagan/Bush: Texas Statewide Telephone Survey - Wave I, August 23, 1980 - August 24, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-004. RNC: Texas Statewide Wave 2, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-004. Reagan/Bush: Texas Statewide Wave 2, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-004. RNC: Texas Statewide Wave 2, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 30)
  - 644-023-005. RNC: Texas Statewide Panel, October 10, 1980 - October 10, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-005. Reagan for President: Texas Statewide Panel, October 10, 1980 - October 10, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-005. Reagan for President: Texas Statewide Panel, October 10, 1980 - October 10, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-005. Reagan for President: Texas Statewide Panel, October 10, 1980 - October 10, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-005. Reagan for President: Texas Statewide Panel, October 10, 1980 - October 10, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-006. RNC: Texas Tracking, October 1, 1980 - November 1, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-006. Reagan/Bush: Texas Tracking, October 20, 1980 - October 23, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-023-006. Reagan/Bush: Texas Tracking, October 15, 1980 - November 3, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-024-001. Reagan/Bush: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-024-001. Reagan/Bush: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 31)
  - 644-024-001. Reagan/Bush: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 32)
  - 644-024-001. Reagan/Bush: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, September 29, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 32)
  - 644-024-002. Reagan Bush Texas Committee: Texas Statewide Panel, October 8, 1980 - October 9, 1980 (Box 32)
  - 644-024-002. Reagan Bush Texas Committee: Texas Statewide Panel, October 8, 1980 - October 9, 1980 (Box 32)
  - 644-024-002. Reagan Bush Texas Committee: Texas Statewide Panel, October 8, 1980 - October 9, 1980 (Box 32)
  - 644-024-002. Reagan Bush Texas Committee: Texas Statewide Panel, October 8, 1980 - October 9, 1980 (Box 32)
  - 644-030-001. Reagan/Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, November 16, 1983 - November 21, 1983 (Box 32)
  - 644-030-001. Reagan/Bush '84: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, November 16, 1983 - November 21, 1983 (Box 32)
  - 644-030-002. Reagan/Bush '84: Cross Sectional Study: Texas, August 1, 1984 - August 31, 1984 (Box 32)
  - 645-007-001. RNC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Utah 1st Congressional District, September 12, 1980 - September 12, 1980 (Box 33)
  - 645-007-002. RNC: Merge, December 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 33)
  - 646-001-001. Reagan for President: A Survey of Republican Primary Voters in VT, November 27, 1979 - December 1, 1979 (Box 33)
  - 646-001-002. Reagan for President: A Panel Survey of VT Republicans, February 16, 1980 - February 17, 1980 (Box 33)
  - 646-001-003. Reagan for President: A Statewide Survey of VT Voters, July 3, 1980 - July 9, 1980 (Box 33)
  - 646-003-001. RNC: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in VT, December 3, 1985 - December 5, 1985 (Box 33)
  - 647-009-002. RNC: First Virginia Statewide Report Extracted from 16 National "Eagle" Surveys, January 1, 1981 - December 1, 1981 (Box 33)
  - 647-009-003. RNC: Virginia Statewide Post-Election Study, November 5, 1981 - November 9, 1981 (Box 33)
  - 647-009-003. RNC: Virginia Statewide Post-Election Study, November 5, 1981 - November 9, 1981 (Box 33)
  - 647-009-003. RNC: Virginia Statewide Post-Election Study, November 5, 1981 - November 9, 1981 (Box 33)
  - 647-009-005. RNC: Voter Attitudes in Virginia From 20 National Surveys, January 1, 1983 - May 1, 1984 (Box 34)
  - 647-009-008. RNC: Merge, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 34)
  - 647-009-009. RNC: Survey of Voter Attitudes in Virginia - Statewide, May 22, 1985 - May 24, 1985 (Box 34)
  - 647-009-012. RNC: A Banner Based on Merged 1984-1985 Data - 'Data Merge, November 1, 1984 - November 1, 1985 (Box 34)
  - 647-013-001. Reagan/Bush: Virginia Statewide WaveI, August 21, 1980 - August 22, 1980 (Box 34)
  - 647-013-001. Reagan/Bush: Virginia Statewide WaveI, August 21, 1980 - August 22, 1980 (Box 34)
  - 647-013-002. Reagan/Bush '84: A Statewide Survey of Registered Voters in Virginia, March 17, 1984 - March 20, 1984 (Box 34)
  - 647-013-004. Reagan/Bush: Virginia Cross-sectional, August 17, 1984 - October 16, 1984 (Box 34)
  - 647-016-001. RNC: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Virginia, February 22, 1985 - February 25, 1985 (Box 34)
  - 647-016-001. Viguerie for Virginia Committee: Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Virginia, February 22, 1985 - February 25, 1985 (Box 34)
  - 648-018-003. Reagan/Bush: Tracking Report of Washington Voter Attitudes, October 5, 1980 - November 1, 1980 (Box 34)
  - 648-019-001. RNC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Washington 4th Congressional District, October 2, 1982 - October 4, 1980 (Box 34)
  - 648-019-002. RNC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Washington 5th Congressional District, September 29, 1980 - October 1, 1980 (Box 34)
  - 648-019-003. RNC: King County Executive Post-Election Survey, November 1, 1981 - November 1, 1981 (Box 35)
  - 648-019-003. RNC: King County Executive Post-Election Survey, November 1, 1981 - November 1, 1981 (Box 35)
  - 648-019-004. RNC: Voter Attitudes in Washington from 20 National Surveys, January 1, 1983 - May 1, 1984 (Box 35)
  - 648-019-004. RNC: Voter Attitudes in Washington from 20 National Surveys, January 1, 1983 - May 1, 1984 (Box 35)
  - 648-020-002. Reagan/Bush '84: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voters in Washington, June 20, 1984 - June 23, 1984 (Box 35)
  - 648-020-003. Reagan/Bush: Voters in Washington, September 1, 1984 - September 1, 1984 (Box 35)
  - 648-020-004. Reagan/Bush '84: A Brushfire Survey of Washington Voters, October 23, 1984 - October 24, 1984 (Box 35)
  - 648-020-005. Reagan/Bush '84: A Brushfire Survey of Washington Voters, October 30, 1984 - October 30, 1984 (Box 35)
  - 650-008-001. Reagan, Ronald: Wisconsin Brushfire, February 1, 1980 - February 1, 1980 (Box 35)
  - 650-008-001. Reagan, Ronald: Wisconsin Brushfire, February 1, 1980 - February 1, 1980 (Box 35)
  - 650-008-002. Reagan, Ronald: Wisconsin Brushfire, April 1, 1980 - April 1, 1980 (Box 35)
  - 650-008-003. Reagan/Bush: Wisconsin Wave 1, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 36)
  - 650-008-003. Reagan/Bush: Wisconsin Wave 1, August 1, 1980 - August 1, 1980 (Box 36)
  - 650-008-004. Reagan/Bush: Wisconsin Brushfire Survey, October 26, 1980 - October 30, 1980 (Box 36)
  - 650-008-005. Reagan/Bush '84: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voters in Wisconsin, August 29, 1984 - August 31, 1984 (Box 36)
  - 650-008-006. Reagan/Bush '84: Cross sectional Wisconsin, August 5, 1984 - October 16, 1984 (Box 36)
  - 650-008-007. Reagan/Bush '84: A Brushfire Survey of Wisconsin Voters, October 25, 1984 (Box 36)
  - 650-009-001. RNC: First Wisconsin Statewide Report from 16 "Eagle" Surveys, January 1, 1981 - December 1, 1981 (Box 36)
  - 650-009-005. RNC: Merge, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 36)
  - 698-003-002. DMI: Ronald Reagan Political Commercials, December 17, 1979 - December 19, 1979 (Box 36)
  - 698-003-002. Reagan for President Committee: A Survey of Voters in the Boston Media Market, February 1, 1980 (Box 36)
  - 698-003-002. Reagan for President Committee: A Survey of Voters in the Boston Media Market, February 1, 1980 (Box 36)
  - 698-003-003. Reagan for President: Comparisons: Five Primary States, December 1, 1979 - December 1, 1979 (Box 36)
  - 698-003-003. Reagan for President: Comparisons: Five Primary States, December 1, 1979 - December 1, 1979 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-005. Reagan/Bush: Two Focus Groups, October 2, 1980 - October 2, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-006. Reagan for President: Panel of Elderly in Florida, Texas, and New Jersey, July 11, 1980 - July 11, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-006. Reagan for President: Panel of Elderly in Florida, Texas, and New Jersey, July 11, 1980 - July 11, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-007. Reagan/Bush: Focus Groups, October 9, 1980 - October 10, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-008. Reagan/Bush: Focus Groups, October 14, 1980 - October 14, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-010. Reagan/Bush 80: Reagan Television Advertising Test III, October 28, 1980 - October 28, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-011. Reagan/Bush '84: A Regional Survey of Voters in Idaho, Montana, Wyoming and Utah, May 31, 1984 - June 2, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-013. Reagan/Bush '84: Television Study "Peace,", June 1, 1984 - September 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-014. Reagan/Bush '84: "Bear" Television Spot Study, October 1, 1984 - October 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-003-015. Reagan/Bush '84: Focus Groups Interview Sessions: Economic Advertising, September 27, 1984 - September 27, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-001. RNC: Televusuib Spot Study, June 1, 1982 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-002. RNC: Television Spot Study "Store,", July 1, 1982 - July 1, 1982 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-003. RNC: Television Spot Study "Postman II,", October 1, 1982 - October 1, 1982 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-005. RNC: Television Spot Study, March 1, 1983 - March 1, 1983 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-008. RNC: TV Spot Study - "Barker,", March 1, 1984 - March 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-008. RNC: TV Spot Study - "Diet,", March 1, 1984 - March 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-008. RNC: TV Spot Study - "Overpromise,", March 1, 1984 - March 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-008. RNC: TV Spot Study - "First Time,", March 1, 1984 - March 1, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-009. Reagan/Bush '84: Transcript of Focus Group Conducted on Theme Tests in Chattanooga, Tennessee, February 22, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-010. RNC: Summary of Focus Group Transcripts, April 9, 1984 - April 10, 1984 (Box 37)
  - 698-005-011. RNC: Regional Nebraska and South Dakota, June 1, 1984 - June 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-013. RNC: Television Spot Study - "Grandfather,", October 1, 1984 - October 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-013. RNC: Television Spot Study - "Bus Stop,", October 1, 1984 - October 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-013. RNC: Television Spot Study - "Thermostat,", October 1, 1984 - October 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-015. RNC: Survey of Attitudes In Rural Farm States, January 15, 1985 - January 16, 1985 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-016. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data for Region I, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-017. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data for Region II, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-018. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data for Region III, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-019. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data for Region IV, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-020. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data for Region V, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-021. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-022. RNC: Banner Report on Merged 1984 Data, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-023. RNC: Banner Report Based on Merged Data 1984 for Region VIII, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-024. RNC: Panel Survey of Public Attitudes in Rural Farm States, October 3, 1985 - October 6, 1985 (Box 38)
  - 698-005-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes in Selected Farm States, July 18, 1986 - July 20, 1986 (Box 39)
  - 698-005-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes in Selected Farm States, July 18, 1986 - July 20, 1986 (Box 39)
  - 698-005-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes in Selected Farm States, July 18, 1986 - July 20, 1986 (Box 39)
  - 699-001-006. Citizens for Reagan: A National Survey of the American Electorate, June 1, 1976 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-011. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-011. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-011. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-011. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-011. RNC: National Survey of Voter Attitudes, May 28, 1980 - June 10, 1980 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-012. RNC: National Survey Of Public Attitudes, January 9, 1981 - January 12, 1981 (Box 39)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 40)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-013. RNC: Post-Election Survey of Campaign & Party Perceptions of voters '"The People Speak" exrpt, November 6, 1980 - November 12, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 699-002-014. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: Eagle II, January 30, 1981 - February 3, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-014. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: Eagle II, January 30, 1981 - February 3, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-015. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: Eagle III, February 20, 1981 - February 22, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-015. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: Eagle III, February 20, 1981 - February 22, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-016. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: "Eagle IV,", March 6, 1981 - March 9, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-016. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: "Eagle IV,", March 6, 1981 - March 9, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-016. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes: "Eagle IV,", March 6, 1981 - March 9, 1981 (Box 42)
  - 699-002-017. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes "Eagle V,", March 25, 1981 - March 29, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-017. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes "Eagle V,", March 25, 1981 - March 29, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-018. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes "Eagle VI,", April 10, 1981 - April 12, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-018. RNC: A National Survey of Public Attitudes "Eagle VI,", April 10, 1981 - April 12, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-019. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VII, May 12, 1981 - May 17, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-019. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VII, May 12, 1981 - May 17, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-019. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VII, May 12, 1981 - May 17, 1981 (Box 43)
  - 699-002-019. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VII, May 12, 1981 - May 17, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-019. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VII, May 12, 1981 - May 17, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Merged data, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Summary of Findings, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Merged data, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Merged data, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Merged data, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Merged data, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Blue Collar), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 44)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Blue Collar), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Blue Collar), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: National Merge Eagles I-VII (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Blue Collar), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Blue Collar), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Females), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes (Females), January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 45)
  - 699-002-020. RNC: 1981 Summary of National Attitudes: Merged data, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 46)
  - 699-002-021. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle VIII, June 12, 1981 - June 14, 1981 (Box 46)
  - 699-002-022. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, June 1, 1981 - June 1, 1981 (Box 46)
  - 699-002-022. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes, June 1, 1981 - June 1, 1981 (Box 46)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle IV, July 16, 1981 - July 18, 1981 (Box 46)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle IV, July 16, 1981 - July 18, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle IX, July 16, 1981 - July 18, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: Social Security--An In Depth Look, July 16, 1981 - July 18, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle IX, July 16, 1981 - July 18, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle IX, July 16, 1981 - July 18, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-023. RNC: National Tracking III, October 1, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-024. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle X, August 12, 1981 - August 16, 1981 (Box 47)
  - 699-002-024. RNC: White House Memorandums, August 12, 1981 - August 16, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-024. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle X, August 12, 1981 - August 16, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-024. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle X, August 12, 1981 - August 16, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: National Survey of Public Attitudes Eagle X, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)
  - 699-002-025. RNC: Memorandum, September 9, 1981 - September 15, 1981 (Box 48)